MSTS CONRAIL LMS C40-8W #720 (repaint of MLT replacement Dash-9)
Original model by MLT.
Glass by Scott Miller.
NS Repaint by Bernard Grant.
Conrail Repaint by Bob Brooks of Steel City Locomotive Works.

Installation: (Original Installation Text by MLT and Bernard Grant, modified by SCLW)

Unzip the download, this will give you a folder
named LMS_D8dash40CW_720 copy this folder to your
MSTS Trains\Trainset directory, then carry out the
instructions in the following paragraph.

To use you will need the following:

Download the MLT Replacement D9 files from here
http://www.mapleleaftracks.com/free.html

Take the MLT Replacement Dash 9 #4723 shape file 
dash9.s, copy it and paste it into the folder 
created above IE:LMS_D8dash40CW_720, rename it 
to LMS_D8dash40CW_720.s

Copyright MLT, Bernard Grant, and Steel City Locomotive Works. (burgerburn)(2006) See
seperate Copyright.txt

Legal Stuff:
Read MLT's and Bernard Grant's copyright info in the MLT_Bernard Grant_Copyright file.

DO NOT redistribute this file or any of its contents, modified or not, without e-mailing:
Bob Brooks: superbirdmm2@hotmail.com

2006 SCLW. SCLW is in no way shape or form associated with the Consolidated Rail Corporation or any of it's holding companies. SCLW is a non-profit organization.
